<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pierre Ouannes</title>
    <link>https://pouannes.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Pierre Ouannes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 02:14:36 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pouannes.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up a First Personal Website</title>
      <link>https://pouannes.github.io/blog/setting-up-a-first-personal-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jan 2019 02:14:36 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pouannes.github.io/blog/setting-up-a-first-personal-website/</guid>
      <description>Having a personal website is very useful, for many reasons. However, building one is sometimes a bit difficult. Of course there&amp;rsquo;s WordPress, but it can feel a bit heavy, and too abstract for someone who likes to code. On the other hand, Web Development is not easy and can be time consuming.
Here I&amp;rsquo;ll describe how I went about making my personal website (this one) and how I deployed it on GitHub Pages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap to ML</title>
      <link>https://pouannes.github.io/blog/roadmap-to-ml/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pouannes.github.io/blog/roadmap-to-ml/</guid>
      <description>This is my roadmap to go from an undergraduate CS and math background to a very good understanding of Machine Learning and Deep Learning concepts, and more importantly to successfully apply ML and DL. I will put here everything I&amp;rsquo;ve done (in italic), I&amp;rsquo;m doing (in bold), and I&amp;rsquo;m planning on doing (normal text) in order to reach that goal.
Courses  Andrew Ng&amp;rsquo;s Coursera Machine Learning course fast.ai course part 1 v3 Udacity Intro to deep learning with PyTorch fast.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://pouannes.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pouannes.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Hello there !
I&amp;rsquo;m a CS student who discovered Machine Learning in 2018 and who has been working hard to learn it since then. I&amp;rsquo;m especially interested in Deep Learning.
I’m a strong believer in self-learning. So in addition to my French engineering school, I take MOOCs and build things to learn and practice. For example, I attended version 3 of the fast.ai course live from October to December — a rather tough planning for me because the classes were beginning at 3 am France time and my engineering class started at 8 am, but great course.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>